Déjà vu is thought to be a trick of the mind... but what if it's not?
Déjà Vu is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Tony Scott.
Called in to recover evidence in the aftermath of a horrific explosion on a New Orleans ferry, Federal agent Doug Carlin gets pulled away
from the scene and taken to a top-secret government lab that uses a time-shifting surveillance device to help prevent crime.
Doug Carlin, played by Denzel Washington.
Claire Kuchever, played by Paula Patton.
Paul Pryzwarra, played by Val Kilmer.
Carroll Oerstadt, played by Jim Caviezel.
Denny, played by Adam Goldberg.
Gunnars, played by Elden Henson.
Déjà Vu is a 2006 American science fiction action thriller film directed by Tony Scott,
written by Bill Marsilii and Terry Rossio, and produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.
The film stars Denzel Washington, Paula Patton, Jim Caviezel,
Val Kilmer, Adam Goldberg and Bruce Greenwood.
It involves an ATF agent who travels back in time in an attempt to prevent a domestic terrorist
attack that takes place in New Orleans and to save a woman with whom he falls in love.
Filming took place in New Orleans after Hurricane Katrina.
The film premiered in New York City on November 20, 2006, and was
released in the United States and Canada on November 22, 2006.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $180.6 million
worldwide against its $75 million production budget.
It was the 23rd most successful film worldwide for 2006.
The film explores themes of deja vu, technology, fbi,
patriotism, new orleans, louisiana.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.